➢ First open the file named game_data in MySQL and execute the
queries.
➢ Then open the file named Project_v3.2 in Python and execute
the code.
A window containing detailed instructions opens.
➢ Click on the explore button to view the interactive periodic
table.
➢ Click on the play button to open the periodic properties quiz.

➢ Instructions for Periodic Table:
   o Click on an element to view its properties.
   OR
   o Type element name, symbol or atomic number in the
   search box and click on the go button.
   o A pop-up box displaying the element’s properties appears

➢ Instructions for Quiz:
   o First type your name in the box and click on go. The quiz
   gets started.
   o Read the question and choose the correct option. Then
   click on the next button.
   o At the end of the quiz, your score is displayed in a pop-up
   box
   o Click on the high score button to view high scores.